&gt；&gt；Steve Kinney：所以我们的代码被解析了，太棒了，
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So
our code is parsed, awesome,
我们一起完成了，我们解析了代码。
we've done it together,
we've parsed the code.
然后呢？
Then what?
您只需将其转换为抽象语法树，
You just turn it into
an abstract syntax tree,
我会给你看维基百科的一句话，尽管我知道这就像
I'm gonna show you a quote from Wikipedia,
even though I understand that that is like
人们做演讲的比喻就像引用维基百科，但是
a trope of people making presentations
just like quote Wikipedia, but
这个很棒，我想我们都应该分享它。
this one is amazing and
I thought we should all share it.
这是维基百科对抽象语法树的定义。
This is Wikipedia's definition
of an abstract syntax tree.
在计算机科学中，抽象语法树AST是
In computer science, an abstract syntax
tree, AST, is a tree representation of
用编程语言编写的源代码的抽象语法结构。
the abstract syntactic structure of source
code written in a programming language.
我们现在都清楚AST是什么了吗？
Are we all clear on what AST is now?
情感上它是什么，就像我们拿了一串文本，
Affectively what it is,
is like we took the string of text,
我们制作了一个数据结构，基本上显示
we made a data structure
that basically shows
实际代码的结构，因为它将被执行。
the structure of the actual
code as it's gonna be executed.
这就是ADD函数的AST。
So this is what an AST for
an add function would be.
在更简单的编程语言中，您实际上只看到蓝色和
In a simpler programming language,
you'd actually only see the blue and
绿色零件，对。
green parts, right.
因为你有一个函数，它有一个返回语句，
Cuz you've got a function,
it has a return statement,
这是你在那里看到的第一个词。
that's the first word that you saw there.
然后它解析该行的其余部分，它看到两个标识符，
Then it parses the rest of that line,
it sees two identifiers,
它看到加法符号。
it sees the addition symbol.
所以我们知道我们将添加x和y，然后解释器可以继续
So we know we're gonna add x and y, and
then the interpreter can go ahead and
开始做所有这些。
start doing all of that.
这里的另一个黄色橙色部分，是JavaScript是硬的。
The other yellow orange part over here,
is JavaScript is hard.
还有像可变吊装之类的东西
And there's things like
variable hoisting and
翻译员需要注意的一大堆其他东西。
a whole bunch of other stuff that
the interpreter needs to be aware of.
以便它还跟踪函数体中的参数和x和y，
So that it also keeps track of the params
and the x and y in the function body,
指向这些参数，然后
point to those params, and
一大堆东西，如果你读过JavaScript规范，并且
a whole bunch of stuff that if you
ever read the JavaScript spec, and
事后醒来，这是有记录的，不用担心。
wake up afterwards, it's documented
in there, don't worry about it.
如果您选择阅读JavaScript规范，
If you ever do choose to
read the JavaScript spec,
第一部分是令人难以置信的有趣和容易阅读。
the first part is incredibly
interesting and easy to read.
但接下来是所有的浏览器实现和所有的规则
But then it's all browser
implementation and all the rules and
沿着这条线的东西。
stuff along those lines.
但我不想劝阻你读它，因为第一部分实际上是
But I don't wanna dissuade you from
reading it, cuz the first part is actually
写得非常好。&gt；&gt；steve kinney：所以我们有AST，
incredibly well-written.
&gt;&gt; Steve Kinney: So we have the AST,
我们拥有制作字节码所需的一切。
we have everything we
need to make byte code.
太好了，好的，让我们把它传给点火，让我们做这件事。
Great, right, let's pass it to ignition,
let's do the thing.
基线编译器获取AST，翻译它，就是这里的这个部分。
Baseline compiler takes that AST,
translates it, it's this part right here.
理想情况下，对，故事结束了，我们不能优化它。
Ideally, right, the story ends,
and we can't optimize it.
它转到字节码，它运行
It goes to byte code, it runs